Hello, salud.
We'll see if you've got any friends.
Dave said he's joining.
It's uh people hear me.
I hear.
Oh, I hear you.
Yeah, we'll see if Dave joins.
Um, I think he said he was coming.
He said he had a meeting right before this.
So, oh, because he had said, um, I didn't check it.
I didn't check the latest.
It moves so fast, it's hard to keep up.
I know.
Are you in Chicago?
Yes.
How's it going?
It's going good.
Excellent.
I did two talks today.
Nice.
Sounds fun.
You had a talk on the birds and a talk on the bees.
No, no.
That would have been a fun talk.
It was actually more mundane and it was a lot more mundane.
It was a talk on our architecture.
Which was actually well received.
An analyst who was particularly neutral on us had nothing but positive things to say afterwards.
How much did you pay him?
Nothing.
Just kind words and willingness to talk to him.
Outstanding.
And not treat him like an idiot, I think, is the extent of the contribution I did.
So, what is this?
I connect to the game and I see a dragon.
What the hell?
Read my summaries.
I provide lots of detailed summary.
I get here.
Where?
I did.
Where is the summary?
It's in a different channel on Discord.
I don't know if you posted one last week, did you?
No.
The last update in Dayton Story so far.
Oh my gosh.
February 25th.
I've been working on creating this, automating my story taking so much that I forgot to automate the most important thing.
The publish button.
Yes.
All right.
Hold on.
There we go.
Anyway, that dragon is in chains.
Don't worry.
It's fine.
No, he's not in chains.
Oh, right, right.
That it broke free.
It was chained.
And it hit you with a.
What should we call it?
Here.
I'm still at full health.
I thought it hit.
Yeah, I thought it was like Brewbarry or something, not me.
Yeah, no, that's what I was gonna.
I said Brewbarry.
All right, so I hit you referring to not me.
There are other people in the world besides me.
I lost 30 hit points.
Yeah, it was.
You'll find them later.
Okay, so here's the snark.
I just posted the snarky version.
All right.
And now the equal version.
I want the longer version.
I put it in the notes.
Okay.
It's in the thread there.
Oh, this was not the snarky version.
This was the more polite summary version.
This was the short version.
I will also put the snarky version because it's funny.
Like I said, I have so many summaries.
Oh, no, that was the wrong thing again.
Yes.
Like that.
Our intrepid band of adventurers decided that the front door of a dragon's mountain fortress was simply too conventional for their taste.
Yeah, that sounds right.
She found Cryovain not lounging menacingly, but magically changed inside a glowing summoning circle performing what could be best described as the world's most ill-advised dragon therapy session.
Yeah.
But it's the cone of freezing death or freezing breath that.
Now it's in the air.
You know, you charged into combat.
You did ask.
Yeah, you did ask, hey, can I do we want to use the ring of fireballs?
Yeah, but you know what the response was.
It's not ours to use.
I know it was even better.
He said, it's probably immune to fireballs.
Oh, it's a dragon.
Yeah.
Okay.
Didn't we find a sword that was supposed to be?
I believe you have it.
The dragon's not really the problem.
Yeah, the Carver is, I guess.
Well, whoever's possessed the dragon is.
Yeah.
Yes, I do have the sword.
Okay.
Yeah, no, you were using the sword.
That was not the problem.
The problem is it's 30 feet up in the sky.
Right.
All right.
Good news is it's completely insane.
As is the party.
Yep.
And the Carver is currently being held.
All right.
We've got little sum over there, so yes, big summa.
Oh, yeah.
I don't necessarily should probably just delete my tokens, but.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
It's just more reminding myself.
These aren't.
Oh, what's this blue circle with a cross inside?
That was where the ritual was taking place.
That was where the Carver's ritual was.
Rudely interrupted.
You know, here I am.
I just, I'm just, you know, that's the word I'm looking for.
A naturalist?
No, I'm just, you know, I'm just an alien entity that's trying to take possession of a dragon, and you guys are too rude to just let me be.
How rude.
It's not like I was going to do anything to anyone other than burn down your favorite town and kill and maim and try to build up my own despotic empire.
Naturalists would have let me go.
Yeah, well, color me an interventionist these days.
A naturalist would have let me go.
They would have recognized me as a natural element and not to be interfered with.
Yeah, they co-opted the language pretty well.
I have to be honest with you, Wade.
The naturalist interventionist thing was inspired by your snark.
Excellent.
I have proved, man.
Since I know how much those things irritate you, I thought this was something that he will enjoy.
Oh, it irritates the fuck out of me.
So I'm hoping you're enjoying it.
I am.
Okay.
Because I did like this.
Was an audible.
All right.
Let me just send a text to Dave.
Is he joining us?
He's here.
He's literally just joining us.
That's okay, man.
Are you okay?
You sound where are you?
I'm in a bathroom.
It sure sounds like it.
Are you legit in a bathroom?
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Is this one of those awkward moments that we should all like turn off our videos and walk away?
No.
I know you're fine.
I said, this is not one of those awkward moments, right?
It's not awkward for me.
Is it awkward for you?
Yeah.
It's only awkward if you make it awkward.
Stop being weird.
All right.
Let's.
Who's going to play Gary's character?
I suppose I can.
So, what was the plan here then, guys?
Plan.
Slay the dragon.
All right.
So let me just to help.
Yes.
So the plan is that the dragon is.
So what happened was the Carver, which was the sword, took possession of the dragon.
Well, it's on route to taking possession of the dragon.
And so the dragon is, and so it has three rounds in which to complete that action.
It has already gone through one round, so we are on the second round.
Okay.
Now the dragon is flying up in the air and unreachable or out of reach of the sword, anyway.
Yes.
But he is enraged, so he's not like, he's not doing the normal thing, which would be to go away.
So you can prepare an action to attack him kind of thing.
If he bothers to calm down instead of just, you know, breathe shit from above.
Yes, there's also that.
So where is the Carver then?
I don't see him in the middle.
The Carver is currently possessing the dragon.
Yeah, he is.
He's transferring into dragon.
Right.
Okay.
You've seen Ghostbusters too, right?
Yep.
There you go.
Here, we'll add some kind of cute little icon.
Here, we'll make him, we'll make him, we'll tint the color purple there.
Right.
All right.
Okay.
So, um, okay.
Hold on.
Why am I not seeing this?
We can begin here.
Yeah, veteran.
Okay.
He's paralyzed.
So I am brown there.
So he gets a.
Is this his saving throw to break out?
I rolled a six, so he's still paralyzed.
He's still paralyzed.
What a shame.
Yeah, no shame.
It doesn't really matter.
He might actually help us at this point.
Who knows?
I don't know.
The sword has been, you know, treating him like shit.
I know about that.
You never know.
All right.
Valphine, you're up.
Oh, that would be me.
That would be you.
Yeah.
Well, whoever's going to play Valphine.
If anybody has any opinions over what she should do, this is a good time to filming.
Does she have Fireball?
She's got a necklace of Fireball beads.
You know, so she looks at you and wonders if she can steal the fireball beads and throw them.
But the necklace?
Yes.
She looks at it.
Yeah, well, then she pauses and reflects on what would Lathander say?
And she thinks that Lathander would like to have her, you know, she's very conflicted.
She's having moments of chaos and indecision.
While I try to figure out how to navigate to Gary's character sheet, she asks herself, what does she ask herself?
Valphine.
All right.
Okay.
Spells.
What spells do I have?
Not fireball.
No, of course I don't have fireball.
That would be that would be too convenient.
There's got to be some area of effect spell that can reach and can do 49 points of damage.
What?
Well, there's guiding bolt.
I'd up-level it.
Yeah, so third-level guiding bolt.
Don't miss.
Guiding bolt doesn't miss, right?
No, it can miss.
Oh, it can miss.
It's not magic muscle.
Does anybody have anything that can help me?
Let's see.
Well, you've got a bardic inspiration, so if you need it, use it.
But you have to roll first.
Oh!
What do you need to hit?
I think I rolled a two.
Well, roll a d8 and see if you can get some more on that guiding bolt.
Oh, I missed.
Jesus Christ, dude.
Dude, somebody else could have rolled.
What the hell?
Oh, my God.
All right.
Well, that was a waste.
All right, Soma.
Yeah.
So what's the overbearing?
Well, so you have a choice.
You can either.
I could either prepare an attack.
Yeah.
You can cast.
You can also prepare.
I can ask Moonbeam.
Yeah, that's probably the best I got.
Make sure Moonbeam goes high enough because it is a.
I think it is strong enough.
I hadn't checked.
I'll do upcast a moonbeam.
Yeah, I just want to make sure it's a cylinder.
Five-foot radius, 40-foot-high cylinder.
He's only 30 feet up.
Yes, he is.
All right, then, yeah.
We'll bring out the moonbeam.
It's the best I got.
And level three for it, why not?
So spawn moonbeam underneath his butt.
And not the best roll, but something.
Concentration tanker.
Bring in a moonbeam circle.
He takes eight points of damage.
Ah, bummer.
Well, it takes him down to 41.
Okay, down to 41.
And I'm going to kind of get out of AOE range, I think.
All right, Brewbarry is up.
Yeah, I'm going to take a moment and put on the circle, but it's all right.
Well, I mean, what can I do here?
You have hand axes.
You want me to throw the axes at the flying dragon?
You could.
I don't know.
Do you have spells?
No.
Well, I definitely do not have spells.
Let me know if you have any other ideas.
Oh, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I just realized something.
Could you check on how tall Brewbarry is when he becomes in giant form?
Where would that be written?
I think he's got 15.
What's his reach?
Your reach increases by five feet.
All right.
So he's...
How tall is he?
It doesn't say it's well reaching.
Your reach increases by five feet.
And if you are smaller than large, and there is enough room for you to increase your size, you become large.
You're not with anything that you are wearing.
Right.
That means what?
I have a 15 feet reach.
And when you become large, what is your height when you become large?
I don't do not know.
Where would that be specified?
All right.
So he becomes large.
Your large form as a bonus for 10 minutes.
Right.
So.
So activate large form.
Okay.
Once per long rest as a bonus action, you can change your 10 minutes.
You have advantage on strength checks and your speed increases by 10 feet, but it doesn't specify the height.
I doubt that I would be able to reach 30 feet, though.
Unless I'm Michael Jordan, I can jump very high.
All right.
So, should I just throw the hand axe?
I guess.
All right.
Okay.
So it increases your feet to at least 10 to 15 feet.
So let's say 15 feet.
And your reach is 15 feet.
So you could, in theory, hit him with the Halberd.
Well, his reach isn't 15 feet with the Dragon Slayer sword.
It would only be with the Halberd.
Yeah, you'd have to use the Halberd.
Yep.
All right.
Well, let's do that.
That's much better than the.
That's probably better than the hand axes.
Yeah.
Say that Guiding Bolt's not there, but that is 11 points of damage.
That's nice.
We'll take 11.
And you get two attacks, right?
Yes.
Right.
Is there a rage bonus that you forgot on any of that?
Yeah, there's a.
Okay.
So I'll.
Oh, yeah.
Rage bonuses, too.
Nice.
And then what's the second attack?
12.
You rolled a 12 or 12 points of damage.
It's 12 points of damage.
I rolled 23.
14 points of damage.
All right.
The dragon was not expecting that.
Did you record the 12?
No, I recorded the first 12.
I haven't recorded it.
It's currently 28.
Somebody has to knock it down to 16.
So 16.
Yeah.
All right.
So dragon is up.
14, 14, 14.
Yeah.
14.
I've got to paste it full rage.
All right.
14.
Thank you.
Ah, he can breathe again.
So who is he breathing on?
Brewbarry, of course.
Bye-bye, guys.
Was fun.
You only need since you.
Yeah, you don't have the deathboard thing, do you?
Sorry.
We'll get you.
You'll be fine.
I mean, yeah, he's like, oh, then Valphine needs something to do anyway.
All right.
Oh, that was cold.
Well, I could reduce damage with the stone's endurance.
Not every type of damage.
I think this one in particular, you couldn't.
No, he could.
That's why it wasn't.
It doesn't say.
It says when you take damage, you can take raging.
His rage cannot affect it.
How many damage is it?
Like 50 points?
I have to check.
Hold on.
How much damage is it?
How much damage?
Everybody's like, I'm feeling pressure, man.
Hold on.
I'm feeling pressure here, man.
I don't like it when I feel teasing, man.
Don't worry.
I know, I know.
45 points of damage.
All right.
So 35.
So hold on, hold on.
I can take the stone's entrance and roll this eight.
Hold on.
You still have to roll your constitution saving throw.
So it's 45.
So roll the constitution saving throw.
Did that roll it?
No.
Okay.
There we go.
Okay, you made it.
So it's 22.
You take 14 points of damage.
Hey, you're still alive.
Wow.
That's amazing.
12 sets.
I've got six points left.
Okay.
He can take two dragon straight to the face.
Yeah.
You're doing great.
All right.
So this dragon is about to die.
Crack.
So where's Carver going to go when the dragon dies?
I guess he's the question.
The dragon flies away.
Now, is it?
Could you read like the dragon flew away?
No, no, he flies away to not be in the cone of radius.
Yeah, it's just going to move next turn, but whatever.
Yeah, I'm just trying to decide where is he moving.
I can't believe that that just happened.
That was like the most disappointing.
Like, if I'm a dragon right now, I'm feeling disappointed.
Two breaths, and you couldn't take down one character.
Yeah, I'm like, this is just like embarrassing.
All right.
Ready?
Ready to die?
Go for it.
Today is a good day to die.
Yes.
Did it work?
Why didn't it connect?
Oh.
Don't ask me how the internet works.
Ask Claude.
All right.
We'll try again.
It's not going.
Well, just tell me what the result is.
Which my roll 20.
I saw the dice roll on my.
Character sheet, yeah, yeah.
It, it, if, if you roll it from your from the DD beyond, it will.
Um, oh, yeah, I see it too.
I see a 13 and a 20.
Okay, well, the 13 was the first one, which is uh, well, 13 plus seven, yeah.
So, so 13 misses, but I can use my bardic inspiration, which is guaranteed to give me at least one, so that's a hit.
Okay, so that's a hit using the bardic inspiration, and then but not a critical, and I roll 2d8 damage 12 damage.
Oh, he's down to two.
All right, I think the moon beam will get him.
Uh, Veteran is up, yep.
Oh, he's still held, right?
We'll see, he's still held.
The whole person spell has been proven to be very still held, excellent.
I love it.
Okay, Valphine, you're up.
That would be you, Costanis.
I know.
What do you guys want me to do?
I mean, like, Valphine's save your friend.
I don't know.
Two points of damage.
Come on, you can arrow at the yeah, the bard will sing songs of you slaying the dragon.
Yeah, can you do two points of damage with your arrow or you miss like usual?
She looks at you and says, I don't think that is what you that the way you want to talk to me right now.
You're supposed to cast vicious mockery on the dragon, not the party.
So she uses sacred flame.
Oh, you don't have tall the dead or anything?
You're your Brewbarry roll.
Victory is on sacred flame.
Really?
What do you mean?
Points of damage.
Shadow heart.
What?
Hey, don't you dare mock Shadowheart, Sacred Fire.
All right, well, that's a guaranteed kill.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, it's save as full save.
So you have to.
What's his dex not a fire?
I have to check.
It's three, so he dies.
The dead dragon.
And the carver and the carver's essence dissipates, and it too is gone.
The carpet is gone for good, huh?
Yes, the carpet.
Campaign over, we win.
Okay, Soma, you can go kill the veteran now.
If you'd like to do non-lethal damage, I see.
Yeah, I'm not a fan of just killing him.
So, yeah, non-lethal.
We can do non-lethal bear claws, right?
Non-lethal bear is fine.
All right.
Wait, wait.
Are you okay with this, Vukradin?
I mean, I haven't quite figured out where you stand on this.
It's non-lethal damage.
He's evil.
I'm the one who doesn't want everything to die.
You're, you know, Vukradin seems more ambiguous about it.
I am enraged at all the corruption and evil that is stying me from my music studio.
Anyway, it's guaranteed crit on the whole person, right?
If you hit.
I mean, okay.
Advantage two, I forget.
He's paradise.
I think so.
I mean, so how much HP did he have?
And those should probably be crits.
So they're.
I always forget how crit is calculated.
Attack rolls have advantage, automatic critical if you hit.
Yeah, how do I add critical damage?
I forget.
Is it just the attack roll again?
But without your bonuses.
Right.
So it's just a so it's 1d8 and 2d6.
All right.
So I'll add those two in.
So let's roll 1d8 and 2d6.
No bonuses on this.
All right.
So he took 20 plus 3 plus 3.
So 26 on 96.
I'm not very good at this.
60.
Sheddy tanky.
64.
If only you had a spreadsheet that would do the calculation for you.
And then this moonbeam comes over and sits on his face.
That does some more damage, I assume.
It does when it moves in.
It does.
17 more damage.
Then he fails, auto fails to save.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
No, Constitution still gets a savings from roll.
He failed.
Yeah, so yeah.
He's down to 47.
This could be.
Brewbarry, you want to finish him off?
Don't kill, don't kill.
He was just a victim.
I think we want to finish him off.
I don't know.
Do we?
Soma would be better off not killing indiscriminately, but you know you might be a little blood ragey after all the damage you've suffered.
I guess.
So I guess we will kill.
I'll try.
It has been decided.
I'm on the record as not being pro-killing, but that's okay.
Ooh, is that a miss?
Yeah.
I have bardic inspiration.
You have advantage.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
So let me roll it again.
There's a head.
That's 11 plus 2.
Where is he?
Oh, no, it's critical as well.
Yes.
14 plus critical.
How do I roll the criticals?
Do we just double the damage?
No, it's just the base of the Halberd.
Whenever the Halberd's base damage is rolled again.
What is the base damage?
There it is.
Okay.
So that will be 20.
So 14, you said, no, 13.
Plus 9, 22, right?
Okay.
And then the second attack.
Yep.
Hold on.
Let me just go down to 22.
And where is the second attack?
There we go.
I forgot to roll it with advantage again.
So let me roll that again.
18.
Okay.
Plus critical damage.
Yep.
All right.
So that's 15 to 28.
Press to 30.
So he's got.
Where is he?
30.
He's dead.
The carver.
Oh, he's not dead.
Did you kill him or did he?
He's unconscious, non-lethal damage.
I don't know.
I thought he was saying kill, but.
So, Brewbarry, did you kill him or did you knock him out?
I was going for a kill.
You're going for a kill, yeah.
Oh, you killed him?
Okay.
Contracts.
Sorry.
No, no, it's raging barbarian here.
Dude.
I'm fine.
I'm fine with that.
Yeah, I'm the only one with somebody.
I'm pointing at him.
And I'm shouting, I win.
You should not pay.
He's always speak with dead, man.
And then I'll come, you know, chomp on you.
No, I'm not going to turn on you.
But I could.
You couldn't stand up to bear.
We owned that combat.
What?
You mean serious owners in that combat?
You have been pwned.
Yeah, you guys did well.
Let's see.
I need to go figure out what happens next.
Sabas, where are you?
I am in Chicago.
You're in Chicago.
Yep.
I am at Nutanix's annual conference.
The fun never ends.
Yeah, invite all of our customers kind of thing.
Okay, where am I creatures in handouts?
I'll still looking at the wrong.
All right.
So I hope this will inspire a song in your new music studio.
Yeah.
We killed the dragon, man.
Valphine did it.
The legend of the great Valphine.
You barely finished, but I already started.
I'll go with we.
We did it.
Where did they put it?
Now we can finally depose the corrupt mayor.
All right.
Well, as you're looking around, so I guess it's loot the dragon.
Loot the dragon.
All right.
As you look around, that the you find a block of loot.
Loot.
Yes.
You mean treasure?
Yeah, it's roughly 3,000 GP worth of goins, gems, and trade bards that have been fused in sort of some residium-infused ice.
Sort of like, and they've melted to all beyond all beyond all recognition.
Oh, the treasure is destroyed.
Well, I mean, it's melted.
Gold is still there.
Yeah, it's treasure slag.
It is treasure slag.
Yeah.
So, um, uh, yeah, and and so the one downside, someone uh roll an arcana check.
Not me.
Dude, my arcana is like negative five or something stupid.
Anybody's got a healing for me?
I got a 10.
I guess Valfina, I guess I should check.
Yeah, Valfina is probably the best.
No, she's terrible.
Oh, that was a zero.
All right, fine.
I'll roll my minus one.
Oh, well, I got a 16.
There you go.
Oh, wow.
Soma for the win.
Soma, who's who's a naturalist, who's, of course, is an interventionist and has been.
Apparently, I am.
And I've become attuned to the events of the interplanar, the interplanar dynamics, recognizes that not only has the ice been fused, but it has been fused thanks to some kind of planar trickery.
So is there like bits of it from other realms or bits of other realms material in there or something like that?
You're not quite sure, but you realize you're going to need to go find a planar theorist who can help you solve this problem.
It's probably being shifted to a Swiss bank.
I also assume that we can't find the owners of this treasure on this plane of existence then, right?
Well, I mean, it's been destroyed beyond all recognition.
So it is, in fact, I mean, you could ask Harbin Wester if it's, you know, conflict-free gold, whether it would be certified as such.
Because, you know, it's any distinguishing markings have, in fact, been destroyed.
Filed up all the serial numbers.
Yeah, they could still file up a claim on how much gold ounces that the yeah, there's no doubt.
Pardon.
All right.
So that's what.
Okay, did we record this on the treasure tracker?
Sorry, this is.
Oh, you got it.
I don't actually, no, go ahead, because I was doing something else.
This is, it's blood.
No, it's not blood.
I think this one.
Are we calling this not blood?
All right.
Why would it not be blood?
Of course it's blood.
There's no distinguishing markings on it.
You could probably, I mean, well, Valphine.
Check what that means it's not stolen, but because you scratched the serial number off?
How do we know whoever returned?
Like a criminal would?
Exactly.
Maybe.
Oh, that last column.
That last column has no label other than zero.
It's just a count.
Actually, I don't know what I don't know what it's supposed to be.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
I mean, you could ask, you can ask the local authorities what they think.
Oh, yeah, you do.
Right.
Because they're so honorable and trustworthy.
Mr.
Puritan.
I think a signer over here reflects its untrusting trust.
Yes.
Never know who's actually true here.
All right.
And as you're as you're reaching, so you as anything else from the dragon?
It's like, you know, parts of dragon or.
Organic fair trade dragon scales.
Oh, parts of dragon.
This isn't scale.
And now that would, that's, yeah.
Bones or scales, that seems reasonable.
We could take that stuff.
I mean, we know who the owner is.
It's, you know, it's like that's not stolen.
That would be acceptable.
Dead men reclaim no treasure.
There we go.
Good luck, ya need a name.
Okay, we're gonna just give me a few seconds.
We should update the quest tracker.
Yes, we have kill Cryovain the dragon with the dragon's third sword.
Tear, tear, go away.
Done.
Wow.
You do have this block of solid whatever.
Treasure slag.
Treasure slag in residium ice iced.
Vukradin.
When you pick up the sword, right?
What sort?
The obsidian sword from the carver.
Yes.
Used to house the carver.
You realize that the crystal that's on the pommel acts as a mental amplifier.
It can project directly, it can project music directly into the minds of an audience, creating a perfect hall-filling sound without the need for a physical building.
It is a portable studio of infinite acoustic quality.
An obsidian sword with a mind-control crystal?
I suddenly missed Jarod.
Why?
Her audiophile commentary on.
Does it say Bose on the pommel?
You're telling me that the sword has a mind control crystal in it?
No, no, mind control.
No, no, it's not a mind control crystal.
It's not mind control.
It's a mind amplifying.
To them.
What's that mean?
I actually don't really know.
Sorry.
It is a mental.
I'm telling you, it can project music.
So here's what it can do: it can project music directly into the minds of an audience, creating a perfect hall-filling sound without the need for a physical building.
Yeah.
People don't need their ears.
It's a Bluetooth pet.
Well, we'll have to find out where that came from because that seems very of infinite acoustic quality.
You don't actually need to build a studio.
You are.
It seems like this was sent by the devil to tempt me.
Yes.
Handcrafted for my personal quest.
Got it.
Thank you.
What?
I didn't hear what you said.
Sorry.
I said handcrafted for my personal quest.
Well, I mean, I'm just telling you, man.
Okay.
So, yeah.
We'll need a legend lore on that one.
Yeah.
So that one is.
So yeah, so that so you realize that perhaps the way the carver took control of the dead, the dead man, is through the use of that amplifier.
Makes sense.
Like I said, this could be for mind control.
Well, no, not really.
I mean, the carver was this particular special entity for non-carver-like entities, it can only be used to amplify music.
It does have, it does have some curious side effects, though.
Okay.
Side effects.
Side effects include being possessed by the carver.
Try using that.
Okay.
What?
Bluetooth 5.1.
That would you guys called it?
All right.
And it's not the Bluetooth sword.
Got it.
Did you just call it the Bluetooth sword?
I'm going to call it the Bluetooth sword.
I like that.
Because it's black.
No, it's not the Bluetooth sword.
It is absolutely the Bluetooth sword.
Done.
No, no, no, no.
This is not it.
This is a mental amplifier.
Magical Bluetooth sword.
Got it.
Sorry.
Thanks for clarifying.
Hey, there was a lot of care and attention that went into the selection of that phrase.
Okay.
So I was thinking, guys, that with the fortress, you know, newly empty, the orcs are all going to move back in, but the orcs are also bad.
Okay, I'm waiting for the thought here.
Hey, like, what should we do about the orcs?
Don't they deserve a place to live?
Well, I mean, so there's a couple of orc groups that you could go target.
There's the orcs that are currently in the Temple of Savras, and then there's the orcs that have taken over the Falcon's Blood.
But yeah, I was going to say the cabin or whatever.
The ones that we ran away from.
Yeah.
That was a bad day.
Well, but we also need to get over to Neverwinter.
I would vote to go to Neverwinter.
So the problem is, I mean, the treasure to return the magical, the return the thing, the person you were going to return it, you missed your window for that.
But you could still go to Neverwinter if you wanted to.
I missed my window?
Yes, there was a choice you had to make.
You made a choice.
I mean, it says have consequences?
Yes.
I still want to go to Neverwinter.
Unacceptable.
Yeah, there are consequences.
So yes.
So you missed that opportunity to return.
Well, I didn't miss it.
No.
Return statue from Lighthouse to Art Collector.
I've already talked about this.
You have to choose between the dragon and the lady.
And so you chose the dragon.
So you're saying that House Markaster has already killed her.
Yes, that has passed.
Well, then, you know, fuck them.
We got to go back justice.
And they're in Neverwinter.
I mean, yes, I said you can go to Neverwinter.
I'm just simply saying the particular individual that you wanted to return it to is no longer available for you to return it.
Well, it's fine.
I wouldn't have known that, right?
I'd be like, let's go, and then we'll find out she's dead.
Yes.
I just wanted you to be with that.
That's totally fine.
You find the next.
Brewbarry doesn't care where we're heading anymore.
There will always be another next kid.
What is Brewbarry doesn't care where we go?
He just wants to get drunk.
Yeah.
I just want to celebrate Victoria.
Hey, man, it's celebration time.
We just killed a dragon.
All right, exactly.
Break out the booze.
You don't have any with you.
I thought, no, no, no.
I thought Brewbarry always had like an entire barrel of wine that he carried around.
He does, but the problem is he drank it.
See, that's the problem.
The whole barrel?
Yes.
Thirsty.
We have like that flask of non-alcoholic booze or whatever.
None of that nonsense.
All right.
So we all know our way to Neverwinter, I gather.
Yes, we've saved.
Could we save Phandalin for now?
I'm sure they'll never thank us, but that's okay.
They'll probably try to take the mayor will probably try to take credit for it.
Okay, so we should ask for a reward, right?
I mean, work has got to be compensated.
You know, just as a side note, you know, roll an intuition, roll insight checks.
With this group of characters, they should all roll disadvantage, and Valphine can roll with advantage.
Oh, I'm going to try again.
No, no, I'm just making a comment.
All right, well, I got just take my first one then.
The 22, yeah.
All right.
So, Soma, you can choose to say this.
You have the insight that Harbin Wester will seize credit for the dragon if you guys don't go and talk to, tell him that, no, no, we are the ones who killed the dragon.
Yeah, I'm sure he will, because he's a fucking asshole.
No, I just doesn't surprise me at all.
You know, the Lord's Alliance will claim credit.
Lots of people are going to claim credit for this.
Yeah, I don't see Soma as caring much about the glory.
So, I don't think she would pass that insight along.
Okay, just you know, I just want Soma realizes it.
Look, look, the universe is safe, right?
Like, or you know, the plane of existence is safe.
That's that's what matters most.
Nothing else, right?
And, you know, the natural order has been returned in the dragon.
My vision, or Soma's vision of the natural order, yes.
Yeah, your natural order is preserved.
I need to get something to drink.
Give me a sec, guys.
All right.
We're driving the GM to alcoholism.
So, why the bathroom, Dave?
Tell us the story.
I don't like stories.
Let's start with the other room.
Okay.
That's better than it could have gone.
So, you're at the hotel.
Yeah.
Okay.
And are you alone?
Are your family?
Where are you?
Well, his son is there, so he's with family, but so where are you physically?
A bathroom.
No, I know that.
Where is the bathroom physically located?
It's in the hotel.
Down the hall.
And where's the hotel physically located?
Oh, come on.
Dave, if you don't want to tell us, don't tell us.
Fine.
Don't you know anyway you get all the rumors from your wife?
You know everything about me.
You know everything that's going on.
No, I don't actually.
All right.
So let's go through this.
We're also in a hotel, but you're alone, so you can take your Zoom call in the bedroom, not the bathroom.
Yes, that is true.
That is true.
All right.
So you haven't explored the rest of this area.
Do you want to explore it or do you want to head out?
Well, I've got six hit points left.
So I suggest you suggest you export short rest.
Okay.
I support short short resting.
All right.
Well, you can recover any hit points.
I don't think I oh, I think I get back one wild shape charge.
That's about it.
I think I get that on the short.
Oh no.
Where the heck is short rest?
Find the short rest button.
Where is the short rest button?
The top right-hand corner.
It's top.
Yes, yes, yes.
Sorry.
My mind isn't working.
And then you have to decide how many hit dice you want to recover.
Yeah.
As many as possible.
Yeah, you should use them all.
Those of us who didn't even, you know, get a scratch.
All right.
So I presume you will head.
So the short rest has been taken.
It was 13.
Okay.
Oh, I did add.
What was my six?
That's 19.
We have sending stones or something like that.
Didn't we get a set of them?
Yeah, you did get a set of them.
But we just have the set, right?
Yeah, yeah.
And, you know, oh, they were actually legit, right?
Like, they weren't stolen.
They were a reward.
Why am I not seeing them in the I don't know?
Did we do something with them?
I don't see them anywhere.
Is it blot item?
No.
Yeah, they're under magic items.
Oh, magic items.
Okay.
I didn't notice there was a column over there.
I was going to send a message to Ser Kaelen.
I don't know how to do that.
Are you still a treasure list?
Where do you see?
It's under party, it's on the initiative tracker.
It's the third tab on the bottom called party inventory.
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, we throw things in all directions here.
Right.
Is there a spell I can use?
Spells.
It's got to be some stupid spell I can use to do what?
That answers the question.
I'd like to continue exploring the room at some points.
Yeah, go for it.
Well, so well, so just as you're you get up there, all right, hold on, see a lean brash woman who's got red hair and it's pulled back into a ponytail appears appears perfect sending and shouldn't see her name.
All right, Sylvine Wintermoon.
She introduces herself and she says, Oh, be praised.
Oh, be praised.
Yes.
Is that dragon bothering you?
She says, she looks at Vukradin and says, Are you Vukradin the bard?
Yeah, that's me.
The one who returns the treasure to those that it has been stolen from?
Well, I haven't done very well with the returning.
Well, thank goodness.
He's got the looting part down.
She goes, Well, me and my brother.
And you see a no, sorry, sister, a muscular woman with black hair and cold blue eyes.
Wait, so she's just been like chilling out in this fortress with the dragon and the carver and like whatever.
Oh, I didn't, I did.
I hold on.
I didn't get there, right?
She goes, oh, thank goodness, thank goodness, thank goodness.
And she turns to the other one.
Runa, didn't I tell you that that saint Vukradin would come and get our treasure for us?
What's this about?
She's like, that she points to the block of you know, slag the treasure slag.
She goes, thank goodness, thank goodness, Vukradin.
I knew it.
I knew that if all we had to do was pray to the gods and a kind soul like Vukradin would come here and deal with that dragon and give us an up and give our treasure back.
Well, that's the quickest we've ever found treasures owners before.
Runa nods her head.
Blessed be, blessed be.
You actually believe them, though.
Jesus Christ.
Lady, I don't know who you are.
I don't know how you think that all 3,000 gold that this dragon forwarded over its long life is somehow yours, but I don't really believe you.
I'm going to need to add substance to your claim.
You're probably going to try to steal this.
Like everybody else, steals.
You're one of them.
She goes, I am.
Why don't you just get out of here?
Get out of here.
Just go.
I am hurt.
You are going to steal.
You should.
You are a thief.
I am tired.
I am tired of all these liars and cheats in this land.
Get out of here.
Phonies.
These goddamn phonies.
There's nobody left worthy.
All right.
Shoe her off.
You try to shoo her off.
She, on the other hand, decides that 3,000.
She's going to attack.
Yeah, she's.
See, I knew it.
Well, yeah, you're stealing money.
Another liar and cheater.
No, no, you are stealing her money.
Now, now you have assumed she's a thief.
I'm not, I'm not.
I'm not stealing anything.
I got to run legend lord.
I got to pay binders fees.
I got to do investigations.
I got to talk to guilds.
Like, I'm not stealing anything.
All right.
Hold on.
Somehow I got to carry around 3,000 gold pieces and not spend it for, well, the rest of the party is trying to unload it behind my back.
Just think of the encumbrance.
It makes the game.
Okay.
Let me.
There's just a couple more.
Things I need to put here.
By the way, whole person is a thing.
FYI.
Yeah, I know.
Short rest doesn't restore spell slots, though.
Yeah, so.
All right.
Let me just put some numbers on these guys.
It does not.
According to my character sheet, I have all my spells, which is weird because I you cast silence and whole person at least.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I used two whole persons.
That's all I used.
No, you swear you started with the silence as well.
That we tried to say.
Yeah, that's right.
I used a whole person and a silence.
I used two second-level spells.
That's it.
And you also used the spell, the whips, the starry wisp.
Yeah, that's a Cantra.
Oh, wow.
That caused that much damage on a critical.
It was a critical.
It was a good crit.
Yeah.
No, it was a good crit.
All right.
There's four of these guys.
Hold on.
What happened to two?
There were two of the other ones to bother me.
What?
So much corruption.
All right.
Hold on.
Let's finish their roles, guys.
My blood sinks full challenge, and they're the next verse.
All right.
Exactly.
Hold on.
Do you want to kill everybody?
She's like, you know, you could have just given us the money, Vukradin.
Yeah, yeah.
Fucking set of cheaters.
What?
Why is every why are you so cranky, man?
I just wanted my goddamn music studio, and I ended up having to go save the world.
You could have your music studio.
All you have to do is to, you know, compromise a few principles here and there.
You don't get it.
No, I don't.
No selling out.
But you have started.
What you do notice is that you have started to acquire a reputation.
Well, I was going to cast a spell before you interrupted this thing, so I guess that didn't happen.
Yeah, so let me just, let me just, I need to do, I need to, I'm going to make sure I'm not doing something wrong with these characters.
I got the 17.
Brewbarry initiative.
I did roll it.
I rolled a seven.
Seven.
All right.
I haven't had my ale, so yeah.
Yes.
And Valphine needs an initiative role.
All right.
She gets a 22.
Nice.
All right.
22.
Yeah.
Use the 20s for initiative.
Yeah, it's the best place to use them, right?
Yeah, Bestest place.
Exactly.
Okay.
Who's first?
Valphine.
Can you use that fireball spell now?
She goes, if I recall correctly, you're the one with the fireball.
Shut up.
I do not have higher fireball.
I think I might need to get a new party that's like more aligned with my values.
I mean, you definitely are at odds with this party.
Good to see you quite a bit at odds.
Yeah.
Here, she's not saying she has any issues with what you have.
She's simply saying you have the fireballs.
She does not.
How many times do I have to explain it?
I don't have it.
Oh, I see.
Oh, oh, I see what you mean.
Oh, okay.
Then nobody has fireball.
Okay.
Fine.
Could you maybe like acquire the spell at some point?
No, I'm not.
The church of the cult of Lathander views the casting of fireballs by Lathandrian clerics to be an affront against their god.
Oh, okay.
Well, don't.
Okay, I didn't realize that.
I'm sorry.
Like, you know, didn't mean to offend your God.
That's not my intention.
So.
Can you kill some things though?
That'd be helpful.
She goes here and she uses her aura.
She casts what's recalled.
Spirit guardians and did 10 points of damage.
They make their saving throws.
Okay, one guy, Sylvine makes it, so she takes five points of damage.
Runa Vokatir Vokdadoyer takes 10 points of damage.
Any way she can walk and hit the other one?
She moved as much as you could.
I share her movement.
I counted.
All right, who's next?
Vukradin.
All right, veteran number two.
Veteran number two marches up to Valphine and wax attacks with their first that is a miss what's her armor cost 82 all right excuse me yeah no no no worries that's also a miss and then a short sword that is uh to d6 25 uh plus three takes 10 points of damage takes seven points of damage okay ten points of damage okay all right and she has to make a concentration check yeah so let me see who that is oh he blows it not not good for the good guys all right she loses her concentration um unless someone can give me a bardic inspiration so i can try to get it try it again uh bardic it's not a reaction everybody has bardic inspiration she already used it because he short rested everybody has it oh okay well then hold on nope that did not work all right who's next i think it's me so yeah bonus action a wild shape there we go there yeah i mean until we have a whole bunch of people wolf isn't so good um and let's see veteran two has already acted so let's look at veteran one uh rolling and 10 points of damage uh the 13s of us yeah 10 and 13 10 and 10.
all right so 10 points of damage on number one yep yep uh so that's two attacks um yeah but the first one didn't hit oh right i was gonna burn bar uh did bardic inspire that one um 28 now right yep so i got a 50 50 actually a little higher than you uh all right they're both hits right so 28 points yep at least the bard inspired and i'll also mark a wild shape oh here i got to 20 points okay okay um wild shape veteran three who's got the who's got the treasure uh me by treasure you mean the the melted gold in the ice yeah so do we want okay um you got it where are you recruiting you're over here he's behind uh dolphin um so you seriously have it right all right so this guy comes here and he will try to take the treasure from you so his sleight of hands against your sleight of hands
Okay, that is a very that is a blow 27.
I think you stole more treasures from them in the exchange.
You tried to do this with veteran number four.
It's not his turn.
Oh, sorry.
I'm a veteran number three.
All right.
So downs veteran number four, yeah?
No, no, Vukradin.
No, it's veteran number one.
Where is he?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just, it's you.
This veteran number.
You're here.
Yeah, I'm just trying to see you.
No, no, no, I know.
I know.
It's veteran number one.
Well, there's a big bear in front of her.
She's going to first.
I mean, first, you fold the treasure.
Maybe tries to.
And the bear gets an opportunity attack.
No, she would move over there, but like, she's like, she sees how she could go like this.
Yeah, as long as she doesn't leave my range.
She can dance around me all day.
All right.
She's going to try to steal the treasure.
Dude, unless you roll a one, you made it.
Me?
You want me to roll again?
Yes.
These people are burning their actions just trying to grab the treasure.
It must be worth something.
All right.
11.
Okay.
All right.
She goes, she shouts, second plan.
We kill them all.
All right.
Is it my turn now?
Yes.
It depends.
Dave, we're waiting for you.
Did Dave's disappear?
The two flanking me can make their wisdom saves.
And let me know if anybody fails.
Well, one of them failed.
And what's your saving throat?
15.
That's two fails so far.
Looks like two fails to me.
Yeah, they both failed to me.
I just wanted to make sure that.
So three and four are held?
No.
Fully out of range.
You've got one.
Who's flanking me?
I can't see.
Three and one.
One and three.
One and three are held.
Held.
Okay.
I'll write it down.
All right.
I'm done.
Actually, since I did that, I can now escape.
Yep.
Yes.
That's cool.
I'm up.
Yes.
All right.
So I go in an instant rage and I yell, try not to die too quickly.
I want to enjoy this.
Or the treasure.
Go for one of the held ones.
You'll get crits and advantage and all that stuff.
Right.
But that would not be sporting.
That would not be what?
Sporting.
He's a drunk, not a not a, you know, kill the easy ones, Brewbarry.
Which one should I hack at?
Let's see.
You should kill one first.
Yeah, one is at lower health, I believe.
Yeah.
Going for one.
Boom, baby.
That's 15 points.
Yeah, you got a critical.
So roll critical damage.
That's what?
18 plus 20?
No.
20, 28?
30.
30 points with 30.
30 with the first attack.
Yep.
Finish them off.
And here comes the second attack.
Here comes the boom.
Dead.
Dead, dead, dead.
All right.
Eight.
Yes.
That's all right.
Veteran four.
Veteran four decides to run.
Root smasher stands, you don't.
That's the story.
That was my victory quote.
All right.
Sorry.
Veteran four decides to run sing.
Screw this shit.
There's more money to be found elsewhere.
Veteran 4 ran away.
Yeah.
Bravely so.
Sir Robin.
Yeah.
No, no.
He's got it there.
He actually says to quote, Well, now that the Carver's dead.
Oh, so he's one of the Carver's men.
Well, or he suddenly realizes that there's an opportunity for a new criminal gang lord here.
Room for advancement.
The opportunities for advancement for those who are alive suddenly, you know, career advancement opportunities suddenly became a lot more interesting.
Got a lot of climbers on the Carver's org.
Yeah, yeah.
He's dashing.
He's like down the hallway.
All right.
I do not care about that guy as long as he's leaving me alone.
Okay.
Who's next?
I think I brings it back to Valphine and then me.
Right.
Valphine.
Or Valphine, then two, then me.
Yeah.
Right.
Valphine.
She's like, run out of Spirit Guardians.
She will.
She has a very interesting word of radiance, right?
Live.
All right.
So you could use an effect both of them.
Okay.
So Valphine will use her word of radiance.
Could it be more useless?
Yeah, I could make their saving cursor.
All right.
Are you like out of spell slots?
Well, she doesn't really have any like spell slots.
Straight offense.
No, like she, yeah, she ran out of spirit guardians.
Okay.
All right.
Next.
Veteran two.
Veteran two sees veteran three paralyzed, sees a bear and sees a drow cleric.
Rar.
And there's Brewbarry.
And there's the barbarian.
And he's going to get all around.
No, it's called disengage.
Oh, yeah.
Disengage.
Okay.
All right.
So, but he it's called disengage and run.
Okay.
Do you guys want to finish off four?
Uh, yeah, I'll bonk three.
I'm not going to go three.
Yeah.
Uh just advantage these unit of advantage.
Auto crit.
Yeah.
For what it'll matter.
Uh that'll be an extra one d8 and two d6.
So one d8 plus two d6.
Is that right?
There we go.
So another eight.
So 22, 30 damage total.
Where did I leave that spreadsheet?
There it is.
30 damage on number three.
Down to 28.
Yeah.
Okay.
28.
All right.
He gets the savings for our role.
Got to try to get out of hold.
Does not make it.
Poor boy.
Who's next?
Does he still help?
Yes.
It's up.
It's you.
You could.
Okay.
Seeing that the combat is going just fine, I'm going to send my message to Ser Kaelen.
Which one?
The dragon is dead.
So is the carver.
We're heading to Neverwinter.
Spread the word.
So you're casting sending, right?
Yeah, I casted sending.
I sent a message to Ser Kaelen informing him that we killed the dragon and the carver.
Okay.
All right.
Brewbarry.
Yep, let me finish him off.
11.
That sucks.
We still have Bardic inspiration.
Yes.
That's all I does hit rolls.
Because your hit rolls auto-crit anyway.
Did Ser Kaelen say anything back?
He can't say back.
It's one-way messaging.
He can.
Look at the spell.
The target hears the message in its mind, recognizes you as the sender if it knows you, and can answer in a like manner immediately.
Oh, okay.
I have to, I think what he's going to say.
Why don't you guys continue rolling, and I will think about what happened.
So I'm sort of lost here.
So let's see.
I rolled 11, and I want to add the Bardic inspiration.
That's a 1d8, is it?
Yes.
Because you don't d8.
But you don't need to, right?
He's held.
You have advantage.
If you're striking the number three, you already have advantage.
Sorry.
As long as you don't roll a one, you crit.
No, no, it's a 22.
All right, that's eight.
Let me roll the damage again.
So that's then 1820.
All right.
Dead.
Because you've got critical damage.
He's dead.
No, no, I already counted the critical.
So he's still got eight left, but I've got a second attack.
Right.
You should be dead.
Good chance of it.
But the second attack, they're going to get it.
Yeah.
25, 11.
He's dead.
Damn.
That was your best.
I'm disappointed and still thirsty.
Drink their tears.
Good job, T.
Good job, tea.
All right.
Ser Kaelen is still thinking about it.
Who are these weirdos?
Hey, man.
Hold on.
Eel and shield for the Order of the Gauntlet.
Hold on, hold on.
No, you see, the problem is he only has 25 words, and he's not a man of few words.
Good one.
For once in his life, he has to be brief, huh?
Well played.
Yeah.
So Ser Kaelen pauses.
He sits there.
He thinks to himself and says, well done.
Well done.
Remember, what was he saying?
Come to Phandalin quick.
Issues with the Emerald Enclave.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
All right.
That's helpful.
Do you share this information with us?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he says that we need to go to Phandalin's.
We're going to ask him back now, which faction of the audience.
Not unless we long rest because I'm out of spells.
Exactly.
No, that's fine.
That's enough motivation.
Unless you decide to get exhausted, you're going to take a long rest between.
You're pretty far away.
Remember, it's yeah.
Well, yeah.
That's fine.
I mean, he's about as close as someone we can actually trust as anybody.
Oh my gosh.
He's moved up in the world.
No, I don't trust him.
He's as close as anybody.
That's right.
He moved up.
So you trust him.
But compared to the previous reaction, you're all crooks, criminals, thieves, and scoundrels.
But we almost trust you.
All right.
No, he goes, he goes.
He goes, I finally have it.
Praise Torm.
Your righteous victory brings light to the north.
The gauntlet awaits your arrival in Phandalin.
We shall celebrate your conflict-free triumph together.
Conflict-free triumph.
I heard celebrate.
Say no more.
Let's go.
We're fighting a fucking dragon.
That was conflict.
Keeping chat CPT.
What?
I liked the first message.
Yeah, I know.
The non-AI.
We could hear the EM dashes.
Yeah, you know, no, I'm just saying.
You could hear the EM dashes.
So, yeah.
So he goes, he does say, praise Torm, who's the god.
That's what I was trying to remember.
Then says, well done.
Glory to the Order of the Gauntlet.
Come quickly.
Issues with, come quickly to Phandalin.
Issues with Emerald Enclave.
Okay.
All right.
We can break there.
Yeah.
All right, good.
Sending actually was useful for something.
How about it?
Got us back on.
I don't think I've actually used that spell before.
Yeah, I know.
I think that's like literally the first time I've ever used a campaign where somebody's used that stuff.
First time for everything.
It's like sending an SMS.
I mean, it's pretty useful.
Yeah, it's like text messaging, basically.
It works across planes of existence.
I know.
It's pretty useful.
Oh, and you can block somebody if they're really pinging you and annoying you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You got a block feature and everything.
Magical testing.
Exactly.
I was like, wait, it's literally got a magic.
It's got a, you know, do not disturb function.
Block feature.
I'm just imagining the guys who put together that stat block.
All right, folks.
Have a good evening.
All right.
Good morning, everybody.
Oh, by the way.
Yeah, by the way, I don't know if anybody noticed the slight pun on the magical item, the item required as a component.
Copper wire.
Yes, for phone.
Has anybody seen my message in Discord as well?
I was asking if any of you have played Coriolis before.
No, I have not played it.
Okay.
All right.
Well, have fun.
Why did you ask about Coriolis?
You have to answer that question.
No, because I'm setting up a campaign with my kids and a friend, and I wanted to get some tips if any of you have played it before.
It's the same system as Mutant: Year Zero.
Yeah, no.
It's a free league publishing thing.
Okay.
Take care.
Yep.
Bye.